Thelner Barton Hoover (UCLA 1930) and Louise Eleanor Brown Hoover (UCLA 1930) photographic collection, 1921-1982. UARC.0647
UCLA Library Special Collections
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Mira Hershey Hall dedication., 1931 Oct 13.; 4x5 black & white nitrate negatives. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Football practice., 1931 Dec 09.; 4x5 black & white nitrate negatives. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Sports, football, tennis, football coaches., ca. 1928-1932.; 4x5 black & white nitrate and safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Sports; Sports, basketball; Sports, football coaches; Sports, tennis; Sports, football; Sports, track. Original negatives maybe found in boxes 27 and 29.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus, 1st snow., 1932 Jan 15.; 4x5 black & white nitrate negatives. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Campus snowfall. Original negatives maybe found in box 27.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus flag., ca. 1932 Mar 09.; 4x5 black & white nitrate negatives. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Royce Hall & Westwood Village., 1934.; 4x5 black & white nitrate negatives. (Box 22, Folder 10)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus., 1936 Apr 25.; black & white negatives. (Box 22, Folder 11)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Aerial views, Goodyear Blimp, UCLA campus & Westwood., 1936 Dec 11.; 2x3 and 4x5 black & white nitrate and safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Aerial view, campus; Aerial view, Westwood. Original negatives maybe found in box 29.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus., 1937-1938.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Original negatives maybe found in box 29.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Gershwin gives "Strike up the band.", 1937 Feb 21.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: George Gershwin & coeds. Original negatives maybe found in box 29.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. UCLA Arrowhead party., 1944 Sep.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 15)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus photos by Paul Sandberg., 1946 Mar.; 5x7 black & white safety negatives (Box 22, Folder 16)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus., 1946 Dec 04.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives (Box 22, Folder 17)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus yearbook photo session., 1947 Sep 15-17.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 18)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Clark Library 4th Annual Celebration., 1948 Jun 06.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 19)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus in snow., 1949 Jan.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 22, Folder 20)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Aerial views, UCLA campus & Westwood Village., 1952 Feb 14-18.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Group portraits, Dodd, Newman, Sparoni, Miller, Sopal, King., 1952 Jun 05.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Paul Dodd, Robert Newman, Sparoni, Gardner Miller, Eli Sopal, Jerry King, Thelner Hoover, Louise Hoover.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Sproul & Moore Banquet., 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 23, Folder 3)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Royce Hall., 1960 Jun 01.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Powell Library., ca. 1960 Jun 01.; 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Dedication of Hoover's Photo Mural (aerial view from 1929) in UCLA Student Union., 1962.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. John Wooden's last game., 1975 Oct 17.; color negatives. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Murphy Sculpture Garden, Song of Vowels., black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Westwood Village & West Los Angeles., ca. 1960-1965.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 9)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Campus commencement., ca. 1960-1967.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Class of 1930, 30th Reunion., 1960.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 11)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Class of 1930, 40th Reunion., 1970 Nov 20.; color negatives. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. 50th Anniversary of the move to the Westwood., 1979.; color negatives (Box 23, Folder 13)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Class of 1930 50th Reunion.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Alumni Association Awards., 1982.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 14)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Sigma Alpha Epislon, SAE fraternity., 1973 Mar 08.; black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity Alumni Banquet.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Sigma Alpha Epislon, SAE fraternity & UCLA Football coach Tommy Prothro., black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity Distinguished Alumni Award.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. ROTC., black & white negatives. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: ROTC, unidentified portraits.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Tower of Masks Dedication, Franklin Murphy., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Ralph Freud & Dr. Kenneth McGowen, Theater Arts Department., ca. 1962.; black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Ralph Freud & Dr. Kenneth McGowan, Theater Arts Department.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Bill Young., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Edwin Pauley & Franklin Murphy., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Tom Davis., 4x5 black & white safety negatives. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Dwight Eisenhower at Charter Day., 1965.; black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Arthur Ashe., ca. 1960-1964.; black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Robert B. Campbell, Campbell Book Awards., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, F. Chandler Harris, Public Information Director., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Erwin (Dutch) Keithley., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 10)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, B. Dyer, Professor of History., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Carmela Speroni, Mrs. Charles Speroni., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 12)
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Louise Brown Hoover, Gold Shield members, & other unidentified groups., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Gold Shield members, Carroll Johnson, Louise Hoover, unidentified group.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, Thelner & Louise Brown Hoover & unidentified UCLA groups., ca. 1940-1970.; black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Alumni Association trip to Hawaii, Louise Hoover & Thelner Hoover; Paul Dodd, Louise Hoover, Charles Speroni (Director of UCLA Summer Session Abroad), Helen Young, William Young, Carmella Speroni, Thelner Hoover.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, unidentified & partially identified individuals & groups., black & white negatives. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Unidentified, Regent Dickson, Chancellor Raymond Allen.
- UCLA. BW Photographs, copy negatives & contact prints. Portraits, groups unidentified., ca. 1940-1970. (Box 24, Folder 16)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. Unidentified photographic materials (no nitrate). (Box 25)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. Brentwood & Bel-Air Women's Club, Paul Welman Luncheon at the Beverly Hilton., 1962 Oct 04. (Box 25, Folder 1)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. Westwood Office Supply staff., 1951 Sep 24. (Box 25, Folder 2)
- UCLA. Glass positives / autochromes & glass negatives. Powell Library, Royce Hall, registration, Louise Brown portrait., ca.1927-1930.; 4x5 glass negatives and color autochrome/glass positive. (Box 26)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Sports, Tennis; Powell Library, 1st registration; Powell Library, Royce Hall, 1st registration; Portrait, Louise Brown (Hoover); Haines Hall.
- UCLA. BW Negatives, nitrate. UCLA negatives, nitrate., 4x5 nitrate negatives. (Box 27)
- UCLA. BW Negatives, nitrate. UCLA negatives, nitrate., 5x7 nitrate negatives. (Box 28)
- UCLA. BW Negatives, nitrate. UCLA negatives, safety., 4x5 safety negatives. (Box 29)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. Campus & Westwood, Pasadena High School, Group portraits., ca.1925-1930.; 5x7, 8x10 nitrate negatives. (Box 30)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. BW & color negatives. Campus, Gold Shield, Westwood Women's Club, Davis Cup, Affiliates., ca.1939-1979.; 2 1/4x2 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 31)
- UCLA & Non-UCLA. BW Negatives & contact sheets. Campus, President Johnson, Davis Cup, Affiliates., ca.1960-1979.; 2 1/4x2 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 32)
- Non-UCLA. BW & color prints. Group portraits, unidentified, tennis, including Los Angeles Tennis Club (Pancho Gonzales ?), travel, "see your west" print folio., ca.1925-1979.; oversize black & white negatives. (Box 33)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: "Landscape, ""Three Graces"" Sequoia Moro Rock Road"; "Landscape, ""Framed in Fir"", Half Dome in Yosemite"
- Non-UCLA. Photographs, some color. Sports - Tennis., black & white negatives. (Box 34)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Tennis, H. Ellsworth Vines, Jr.; Tennis, Frederick J. Perry, J. Donald Budge; Tennis, Jack Kramer; Tennis, Winners 1934 PSW at Los Angeles Tennis Club, Sarah Palfrey, Alice Marble, Elizabeth Ryan, Gene Mako, John Van Ryan, J. Donald Budge, Wilmer Allison, Dorothy Round, Frederick J. Perry, H. Ellsworth Hines, & Lester R. Stoefen; Tennis, Arthur Ashe.
- Non-UCLA. Photographs, some color. Las Floristas. (Box 35)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs, some color. Brides & weddings. (Box 36)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs, some color. Brides & weddings. (Box 37)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Women's group portraits & events. (Box 38)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Events, Beverly Wilshire. (Box 39)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Events, Ronald & Nancy Reagan. (Box 40)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Portraits, Celebrities, some unidentified., Black & white negatives. (Box 41)
  This folder includes negatives of the following: Artur Rubenstein, pianist & companion; Prince Rainier III of Monaco, Albert, Caroline, Stephanie, Princess Grace of Monaco; Princess Grace of Monaco, Stephanie, Caroline, Albert, Prince Rainier III of Monaco; Prince Rainier III of Monaco, Albert, Stephanie, Princess Grace of Monaco; Richard Nixon and unidentified group; Natalie Wood, actress and unidentified group; Sybil Brand & Ceasar Romero, actor; Edith Head, Yves St. Laurent, Mrs. Hernando Courtright; Hernando Courtright, Beverly Wilshire Hotel owner, Yves St. Laurent, Mrs. Hernando Courtright; Yves St. Laurent, unidentified, Mrs. Hernando Courtright, Hernando Courtright, Beverly Wilshire Hotel owner.
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events. (Box 42)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events. (Box 43)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events. (Box 44)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events. (Box 45)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events. (Box 46)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Portraits, individual & families. (Box 47)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Portraits, individual & families. (Box 48)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Architecture & commercial products. (Box 49)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events., 1965. (Box 50)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events., 1966. (Box 51)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events., 1966. (Box 52)
- Non UCLA(?). Photographs. Group portraits & events., 1967. (Box 53)
- Non-UCLA. Color photographs. Portraits & travel. (Box 54)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Alpha Xi Delta, Sun Valley Idaho., 1968 Jun 20-25. (Box 55)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Delta Zeta. (Box 56, Box 57)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family & travel. (Box 58, Box 59)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs, negatives, slides, book. Hoover family. (Box 60)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family given by Keith Brown., 1996 Dec. (Box 61)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family. (Box 62, Box 63, Box 64)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family, old photos of earlier family generations. (Box 65)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family. (Box 66, Box 67, Box 68)
- Non-UCLA.Photographs, some color. Hoover family. (Box 69)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family. (Box 70)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Early work by Thelner Hoover, landscapes. (Box 71)
- Non-UCLA.Photographs, some color. Hoover family. (Box 72)
- Non-UCLA.Photograph albums. Hoover family. (Box 73)
- Non-UCLA. Daguerrotypes, tintypes. Hoover family. (Box 74)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Hoover family. (Box 75)
- Non-UCLA. Photographs. Unidentified. (Box 76)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Portraits & Weddings., 1965-1969.; 4x5 safety negatives. (Box 77)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 1933-1975.; 4x5 safety negatives. (Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83, Box 84, Box 85, Box 86)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Tennis, Las Floristas & others., 1936-1972.; 2 1/4, 35mm safety negatives. (Box 87)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Delta Zeta, Sigma Alpha Epsilon & Alpha Delta Theta., 1964-1978.; 2 1/4, 4x5 safety negatives. (Box 88)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Alpha Delta Theta & Alpha Xi Delta., 1961.; 2 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 89)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Las Floristas., 1969-1976.; 3 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 90)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Beverly Wilshire & others., 1964-1970.; 4 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 92)
- Non-UCLA. Negatives. Beverly Wilshire & others., 1966-1975.; 5 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 93)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 1964-1978.; 6 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 94)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 1960-1979.; 7 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 95)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 1970-1976.; 8 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 96)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 9 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 97)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 10 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 98)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 11 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 99)
- Non-UCLA? Negatives. Unidentified., 12 1/4 safety negatives. (Box 100)
- Non-UCLA. Slides in cases. Travel, Hoover family, 7 parks & Canada., 1940. (Box 101)
- Non-UCLA? Slides in cases. Travel, Alaska., 1938. (Box 102)
- Non-UCLA? Slides in cases. Travel, Southwest Grand Canyon. (Box 103)
- Non-UCLA? Slides. Travel. (Box 104, Box 105)
- Non-UCLA? Slides. Trave, Bangkok, Tokyo, Australia, Bali, New Zealand. (Box 106)
- Non-UCLA? Slides. Travel. (Box 107)
- Non-UCLA? Slides. Travel & miscellaneous unidentified. (Box 108)
- Non-UCLA. 5 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, travel to Hawaii, Europe., ca.1951. (Box 109)
- Non-UCLA. 6 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, holidays. (Box 110)
- Non-UCLA. 6 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, travel to Guatemala, Europe. (Box 111)
- Non-UCLA. 6 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, travel to Mexico, Grand Canyon & Sports - football USC vs. Notre Dame. (Box 112)
- Non-UCLA. 2 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, travel to Hawaii & a sound track. (Box 113)
- Non-UCLA. 2 reels 32mm film. Hoover family, travel to Ohio & Headdress Ball, Las Floritas 1964., ca.1964. (Box 114)
- UCLA. 6 reels 16mm color film. Jr. at AMIGS 1937 Discards. 1950 PJC. Medical bldg. June 2, 1952 in construction. 1951 medical school construction site ceremony. La Brea Avenue ca. 1955. View from Marshall Field., 16mm film color film. (Box 115)
  Scope and Content
  Films labeled
- Non-UCLA. 6 reels 16mm film. Ten Happy Years. Tennis 1948. 1932 Pacific Southwest Tennis with Allison Van Ryan, 2 reels. Tennis, n.d. Christmas at Nans 1971. (Box 116)
- Non-UCLA. Miscellaneous films., 16mm film. (Box 117)
- Non-UCLA. 24 reels 16mm film. Hoover family, travel to Alaska, Canada, Mexico, and Yosemite., 1934-1951.; Includes color and black and white safety film.